YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 7. Student Work
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES XI. STUDENT ASSOCIATIONS AND REGISTERED STUDENT GROUPS
  - General
    - Study on proposed changes in purpose and basis of membership policies and practices, 1957-58 (Box 787, Folder 6)
  - Membership
    - Accreditation requirements, 1982-96 (Box 787, Folder 7)
    - Affiliation/Disaffiliation, 1940-62, 1980-98, n.d. (Box 787, Folder 8-9)
    - Committees
      - Purpose Commission, 1925-27 (Box 787, Folder 10)
      - Student Standards Study Committee, 1939-40 (Box 787, Folder 11-12)
      - Student Constitution and Standards Committee/Standards Committee, 1949-56 (Box 787, Folder 13)
      - Committee on Member Associations, College and University Division, 1958-63 (Box 787, Folder 14)
      - Life and Work Committee, 1965-66 (Box 787, Folder 15)
      - Membership in the National Association (MINA) Committee, student matters, 1984-2000 (Box 787, Folder 16-18)
    - Financial: Fair Share, 1965-92 (Box 788, Folder 1)
    - Forms and Guidelines
      - Miscellaneous, 1953-97, n.d. (Box 788, Folder 2)
      - Annual Report, 1951-97 (Box 788, Folder 3)
      - Basic Standards Report forms, 1952-70 (Box 788, Folder 4)
      - Basic Standards Report, 1952-61 (Box 788, Folder 5)
      - Association Review, 1983 (Box 788, Folder 6)
      - Brief Information Basic to Organizing a Student YWCA on Your Campus/How to Organize a Student YWCA on Your Campus, 1974-96 (Box 788, Folder 7)
      - Suggested Constitution for a Student YWCA, 1908-13, 1970, n.d. (Box 788, Folder 8)
      - How to Organize a Student YWCA on Your Campus: Advisers Manual, 1995-96 (Box 788, Folder 9)
      - Student Action Audit for Change, 1970-80 (Box 788, Folder 10)
  - Association Files
    - Alabama: Alabama State University, 1983 (Box 788, Folder 11)
    - Arizona: Arizona State University, Women's Student Center (RSG), 1986-95, n.d. (Box 788, Folder 12)
    - Arkansas: Philander-Smith College, 1979 (Box 788, Folder 13)
    - California
      - California State University at Fresno, 1951-84, n.d. (Box 788, Folder 14-15)
      - California, University of
        - Berkeley, [see also Record Group 8, Community Associations Files, California, Berkeley]
          - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1986-2001 (Box 788, Folder 16-17)
          - Board of Directors, 1981-83, 1991-98 (Box 788, Folder 18)
          - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1972-98 (Box 789, Folder 1)
          - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1975-2000, n.d. (Box 789, Folder 2-3)
          - Financial, 1994-96 (Box 789, Folder 4)
          - History "Standing Ground and Starting Point," 1990 (Box 789, Folder 5)
          - Program, 1988-2001, n.d. (Box 789, Folder 6-9)
        - Davis, Cal Aggie Christian Association (RSG)
          - 1969-79 (Box 789, Folder 10)
          - 1980-96 (Box 790, Folder 1)
        - Los Angeles, [see also Record Group 8, Community Associations Files, California, Los Angeles, Greater]
          - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1968/69, 1985-93 (Box 790, Folder 2)
          - Board of Directors, 1981-94 (Box 790, Folder 3)
          - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1924-88 (Box 790, Folder 4)
          - Correspondence and Campus Visit reports, 1974-98, n.d. (Box 790, Folder 5-6)
          - Program, 1988-93, n.d. (Box 790, Folder 7)
      - Humboldt State University, Club O, 1993 (Box 790, Folder 8)
      - Pacific, University of the, Anderson Y Center, Stockton
        - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1948-80, n.d. (Box 790, Folder 9)
        - General, 1973-96, n.d. (Box 790, Folder 10)
    - San Diego State University, 1969-95 (Box 790, Folder 11)
    - Southern California, University of, 1980-90 (Box 790, Folder 12)
    - Stanford University, 1958-88, [see also Record Group 8, Community Associations Files, California, Mid-Peninsula] (Box 790, Folder 13)
  - Colorado
    - Colorado, University of-Boulder, 1970-79 (Box 790, Folder 14)
    - Colorado Women's College, 1979 (Box 790, Folder 15)
    - Denver, University of, 1955-79, n.d. (Box 790, Folder 16-17)
  - District of Columbia: Howard University
    - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1987, 1997, n.d. (Box 790, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence and Campus Visit reports, 1981-99, n.d. (Box 790, Folder 19-20)
    - Program, circa 1980-98 (Box 790, Folder 21)
  - Florida: Bethune-Cookman College, 1982, 1992 (Box 790, Folder 22)
  - Georgia
    - Agnes Scott College, 1979 (Box 790, Folder 23)
    - Berry College, 1979 (Box 790, Folder 24)
    - Clark College, 1982, 1993 (Box 790, Folder 25)
    - Morris Brown College, 1993 (Box 790, Folder 26)
    - Spelman College, 1981-93 (Box 790, Folder 27)
  - Hawaii, University of Hawaii, [see also Record Group 8, Community Associations Files, Hawaii, O'ahu]
    - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1984-2001 (Box 790, Folder 28-29)
    - Board of Directors, 1980-96 (Box 791, Folder 1)
    - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1955-94, n.d. (Box 791, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1943-49, 1969-99, n.d. (Box 791, Folder 3-6)
    - Program, 1969-98, n.d. (Box 791, Folder 7)
  - Idaho: Boise State University
    - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1990-94 (Box 791, Folder 8)
    - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1989-94 (Box 791, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1988-98, n.d. (Box 791, Folder 10)
  - Illinois
    - Illinois State Normal University, Normal, IL, circa 1884, 1916-49 (Box 791, Folder 11)
    - Northwestern University, 1943-44 (Box 791, Folder 12)
    - University of, Champaign-Urbana (formerly Illinois Industrial University)
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1987-2001 (Box 791, Folder 13-14)
      - Action Audit, 1975-76 (Box 792, Folder 1)
      - Board of Directors, 1982-2000 (Box 792, Folder 2-3)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1969-98 (Box 792, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1874-75, 1911, 1966-2001, n.d. (Box 792, Folder 5-8)
      - Program, 1980-2000, n.d. (Box 792, Folder 9-12)
  - Iowa
    - Iowa State Teachers College, Cedar Falls, IA, 1931-33 (Box 792, Folder 13)
    - Iowa State University/Ames-ISU
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1984-2001 (Box 793, Folder 1-3)
      - Action Audit, 1980 (Box 793, Folder 4)
      - Board of Directors, 1992-2000, n.d. (Box 793, Folder 5-6)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1964-96 (Box 793, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1973-2000, n.d. (Box 793, Folder 8-9)
      - Program, 1992-2000, n.d. (Box 793, Folder 10-11)
    - Southwestern Community College, 1969-76 (Box 793, Folder 12)
  - Kansas: University of Kansas, 1970-71, 1981-84 (Box 793, Folder 13)
  - Kentucky: University of Kentucky, 1988-98, n.d. (Box 793, Folder 14-15)
  - Louisiana
    - Dillard University, 1972-76, n.d. (Box 793, Folder 16)
    - Grambling College/State University, 1964-80 (Box 794, Folder 1)
    - Southern University
      - General, 1962-84 (Box 794, Folder 2)
      - Student slayings, 1972-73 (Box 794, Folder 3)
  - Maryland
    - Frostburg State College, 1979 (Box 794, Folder 4)
    - Maryland, University of, 1979 (Box 794, Folder 5)
    - Morgan State University
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1988-2001 (Box 794, Folder 6-7)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1969, 1994 (Box 794, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1973-99, n.d. (Box 794, Folder 9-10)
    - Towson State College, 1979 (Box 794, Folder 11)
  - Massachusetts
    - Salem State College (RSG), 1993, 1996 (Box 794, Folder 12)
    - Simmons College (RSG), 1988, 1992-96 (Box 794, Folder 13)
  - Michigan
    - University of Michigan: report, 1958 (Box 794, Folder 14)
  - Minnesota
    - Austin Junior College, 1979 (Box 794, Folder 15)
    - Minnesota, University of
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1985-2001 (Box 794, Folder 16-18)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1986-98, n.d. (Box 794, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1978-99 (Box 794, Folder 20-21)
      - Legal
        - 1981-96 (Box 794, Folder 22)
        - 1997-98, n.d. (Box 795, Folder 1)
      - Program, 1970s, 1990s, n.d. (Box 795, Folder 2-3)
    - Rochester State Junior College, 1979 (Box 795, Folder 4)
  - Mississippi
    - Alcorn State University/Alcorn A. and M. College
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1967-71, 1991-2001 (Box 795, Folder 5)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1969-94, n.d. (Box 795, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1965-99 (Box 795, Folder 7-8)
    - Harris Junior College, 1964 (Box 795, Folder 9)
    - Hinds Junior College, 1973-77 (Box 795, Folder 10)
    - Jackson State University/College, 1969-86 (Box 795, Folder 11)
    - Millsaps College, 1965-77, n.d. (Box 795, Folder 12)
    - Mississippi Industrial College, 1964-84 (Box 795, Folder 13)
    - Mississippi State College for Women/Mississippi University for Women, 1968-78, n.d. (Box 795, Folder 14)
    - Mississippi, University of, 1962-74 (Box 795, Folder 15)
    - Mississippi Valley State University, 1983-93 (Box 795, Folder 16)
    - Prentiss Normal and Industrial Institute, 1972-84, n.d. (Box 795, Folder 17)
    - Rust College, 1968-85, n.d. (Box 795, Folder 18)
    - Tougaloo College, 1969-74 (Box 795, Folder 19)
  - Missouri
    - Cottey College, 1981 (Box 795, Folder 20)
    - Missouri, University of-Columbia, 1984-85 (Box 795, Folder 21)
    - Washington University, Campus Y, [see also Record Group 8, Community Associations Files, Missouri, St. Louis]
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports
        - 1968-1993/94 (Box 795, Folder 22-23)
        - 1995-2001 (Box 796, Folder 1)
      - Board of Directors, 1989-99, n.d. (Box 796, Folder 2)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1996 (Box 796, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1975-99 (Box 796, Folder 4)
      - Program, 1963-2001, n.d. (Box 796, Folder 5-6)
    - William Woods College
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1964-87 (Box 796, Folder 7)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1965-90, n.d. (Box 796, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1959-88, n.d. (Box 796, Folder 9)
  - Nebraska, University of
    - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1956, 1968-81, n.d. (Box 796, Folder 10-11)
    - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1956-76, n.d. (Box 796, Folder 12-13)
    - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports
      - 1954-60 (Box 796, Folder 14)
      - 1961-84, n.d. (Box 797, Folder 1-5)
    - History, 1959, 1973, 1981 (Box 797, Folder 6)
    - Program, 1956-81, n.d. (Box 797, Folder 7-8)
  - Nevada, University of, 1967-75 (Box 797, Folder 9)
  - New York: Syracuse University, 1985 (Box 797, Folder 10)
  - North Carolina
    - Appalachian State Teachers' College, 1964-66 (Box 797, Folder 11)
    - Barber-Scotia College, 1965 (Box 797, Folder 12)
    - Bennett College
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1966-78 (Box 797, Folder 13)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1910, 1963-64 (Box 797, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1965?-80, n.d. (Box 797, Folder 15)
    - Catawba College, 1965-78, n.d. (Box 797, Folder 16)
    - Charlotte College/UNC-Charlotte, 1962-63 (Box 797, Folder 17)
    - Duke University
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1968-78 (Box 797, Folder 18-19)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1969-72, n.d. (Box 798, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1961-83 (Box 798, Folder 2)
      - Program, 1973-79, n.d. (Box 798, Folder 3)
    - East Carolina University, 1970-77 (Box 798, Folder 4)
    - Guilford College, 1964-65 (Box 798, Folder 5)
    - Johnson C. Smith University, 1980-81 (Box 798, Folder 6)
    - Lenoir-Rhyne College, 1964-65 (Box 798, Folder 7)
    - Livingstone College, 1965-75 (Box 798, Folder 8)
    - Louisburg College, 1966 (Box 798, Folder 9)
    - North Carolina Agricultural and Technical State College/University, 1967-68, 1981-84 (Box 798, Folder 10)
    - North Carolina Central University
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1992-2001 (Box 798, Folder 11)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1981-98 (Box 798, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1965, 1980-99, n.d. (Box 798, Folder 13)
    - North Carolina, University of-Chapel Hill
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1969-75, 1983/84-96 (Box 798, Folder 14-17)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1964-97 (Box 798, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1965-99, n.d. (Box 798, Folder 19-21)
      - Program, 1974-97, n.d. (Box 799, Folder 1)
    - Queens College, 1966-71, n.d. (Box 799, Folder 2)
    - Salem College, 1965-73, n.d. (Box 799, Folder 3)
    - Shaw University, 1965 (Box 799, Folder 4)
    - Winston-Salem State University, 1965-93, n.d. (Box 799, Folder 5)
  - Ohio
    - Central State University, 1980 (Box 799, Folder 6)
    - Miami University, 1980 (Box 799, Folder 7)
    - Oberlin College, 1975-98, n.d. (Box 799, Folder 8)
    - Ohio State University, 1935-84 (Box 799, Folder 9)
    - Ohio Wesleyan University
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1966-84 (Box 799, Folder 10-12)
      - Board of Directors, 1968-78 (Box 799, Folder 13)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1967-75, n.d. (Box 799, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1968-95, n.d. (Box 799, Folder 15-18)
      - Program
        - 1968-79 (Box 799, Folder 19-20)
        - 1980-91, n.d. (Box 800, Folder 1)
    - Otterbein College, 1979 (Box 800, Folder 2)
    - Toledo, University of, 1979 (Box 800, Folder 3)
    - Wilberforce University, 1979 (Box 800, Folder 4)
  - Oklahoma
    - Central State College: history, 1961 (Box 800, Folder 5)
  - Oregon
    - Lane Community College (RSG), 1988 (Box 800, Folder 6)
    - Linfield College, 1979 (Box 800, Folder 7)
    - Oregon State University
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1984-98 (Box 800, Folder 8-9)
      - Board of Directors, 1975-91 (Box 800, Folder 10)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1950-98, n.d. (Box 800, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1969-99, n.d. (Box 800, Folder 12-13)
      - Program, 1967-98, n.d. (Box 800, Folder 14-16)
    - Oregon, University of
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1978-85, 1990-2001 (Box 800, Folder 17-18)
      - Board of Directors, 1981, 1988, 1991, 1995, n.d. (Box 801, Folder 1)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1964-98, n.d. (Box 801, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1971-2000, n.d. (Box 801, Folder 3-6)
      - Program, 1968-95, n.d. (Box 801, Folder 7)
    - Portland State University, 1994 (Box 801, Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania
    - Albright College, 1971-78 (Box 801, Folder 9)
    - Carnegie-Mellon University, 1964-74 (Box 801, Folder 10)
    - Cheyney State College, 1980 (Box 801, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh, University of, 1970-83 (Box 801, Folder 12)
  - South Carolina
    - Allen University, 1963-71 (Box 801, Folder 13)
    - Benedict College, 1963-72 (Box 801, Folder 14)
    - Converse College, 1966-71 (Box 801, Folder 15)
    - Erskine College, 1965-79, n.d. (Box 801, Folder 16)
    - Furman University, 1965-67 (Box 801, Folder 17)
    - Morris College, 1972, 1979 (Box 801, Folder 18)
    - Newberry College, 1963-71 (Box 801, Folder 19)
    - South Carolina State College, 1969-82 (Box 801, Folder 20)
    - South Carolina, University of, 1965-75, n.d. (Box 801, Folder 21)
    - Voorhees College, 1966-72 (Box 801, Folder 22)
  - Tennessee
    - Fisk University, 1967-80, n.d. (Box 801, Folder 23)
    - Knoxville College, 1964-80 (Box 801, Folder 24)
    - Lane College, 1964-69 (Box 801, Folder 25)
    - LeMoyne College, 1965 (Box 801, Folder 26)
    - Maryville College, 1964, 1972 (Box 801, Folder 27)
    - Memphis University, 1972 (Box 801, Folder 28)
    - Morristown College, 1964-68 (Box 801, Folder 29)
    - Tennessee [Agricultural and Industrial] State University, 1964-75 (Box 802, Folder 1)
    - Tennessee, University of, 1967 (Box 802, Folder 2)
    - Vanderbilt University, 1964-67 (Box 802, Folder 3)
  - Texas
    - Del Mar College, 1964-66 (Box 802, Folder 4)
    - Jarvis Christian College, 1950-51, 1975 (Box 802, Folder 5)
    - Prairie View A & M, 1965, 1984 (Box 802, Folder 6)
    - Southern Methodist University
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1968-98 (Box 802, Folder 7-8)
      - Board of Directors, 1965-98, n.d. (Box 802, Folder 9)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1966-99 (Box 802, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1964-2000, n.d. (Box 802, Folder 11-15)
      - Program, 1967-93, n.d. (Box 802, Folder 16)
    - Southwestern University, 1964-65 (Box 802, Folder 17)
    - Texas Christian University, 1964-66 (Box 802, Folder 18)
    - Texas Southern University, 1964-66 (Box 802, Folder 19)
    - Texas, University of-Austin, [see also Record Group 8, Community Associations, Texas, Austin]
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports
        - 1969-77 (Box 802, Folder 20)
        - 1978, 1986-98 (Box 803, Folder 1-3)
      - Board of Directors, 1970-97, n.d. (Box 803, Folder 4-5)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1958-97, n.d. (Box 803, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports (Box 803)
        - 1960-95 (Box 803, Folder 7-11)
        - 1996-99, n.d. (Box 804, Folder 1)
      - Program, 1960s-90s, n.d. (Box 804, Folder 2-3)
    - Wiley College, 1922, 1980 (Box 804, Folder 4)
  - Virginia
    - Bridgewater College, 1963-69 (Box 804, Folder 5)
    - Hampton Institute, 1915-80 (Box 804, Folder 6)
    - Longwood College, 1962-72 (Box 804, Folder 7)
    - Madison College, 1963-71 (Box 804, Folder 8)
    - Mary Washington College, 1962-70, n.d. (Box 804, Folder 9)
    - Radford College, 1963-70 (Box 804, Folder 10)
    - Randolph-Macon Woman's College, 1965-82 (Box 804, Folder 11-12)
    - Southern Seminary, 1962-72 (Box 804, Folder 13)
    - Sweet Briar College, 1961-82, n.d. (Box 804, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1964 (Box 804, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Seminary, 1967 (Box 804, Folder 16)
    - Virginia State College-Norfolk/Norfolk State College, 1963-78 (Box 804, Folder 17)
    - Virginia State College-Petersburg, 1969-79 (Box 804, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Union University, 1964 (Box 804, Folder 19)
    - Westhampton College of the University of Richmond, 1962-76, n.d. (Box 804, Folder 20)
  - Washington
    - Everett Community College (RSG), 1988 (Box 804, Folder 21)
    - The Evergreen State College, 1988-99 (Box 804, Folder 22)
    - Shoreline Community College (RSG), 1988 (Box 804, Folder 23)
    - Spokane Falls Community College, Associated Women Students (RSG), 1990-96 (Box 804, Folder 24)
    - Tacoma Community College, Women into the Future (RSG), 1994-96 (Box 805, Folder 1)
    - Washington State College/University, Pullman, WA
      - Report of General Director, 1936-37 (Box 805, Folder 2)
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports, 1975-2001 (Box 805, Folder 3-6)
      - Board of Directors, 1974-97, n.d. (Box 805, Folder 7)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1954-96 (Box 805, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports, 1970-79, 1988-99, n.d. (Box 805, Folder 9-13)
      - Program
        - 1968-79 (Box 805, Folder 14)
        - 1980-96, n.d. (Box 806, Folder 1-3)
    - Washington, University of
      - Accreditation and Annual Reports
        - 1953, 1978, 1985-99 (Box 806, Folder 4-6)
      - Board of Directors, 1969, 1978-79, 1992-93 (Box 806, Folder 7-8)
      - Constitution and Basic Documents, 1971-97, n.d. (Box 806, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence and Campus Visit Reports
        - 1968-92 (Box 806, Folder 10-14)
        - 1993-99, n.d. (Box 807, Folder 1-2)
      - Program, 1968-98, n.d. (Box 807, Folder 3-4)
    - Western Washington College, 1979 (Box 807, Folder 5)
    - Whitman College Women's Resource Center (RSG), 1988-96 (Box 807, Folder 6)
  - West Virginia
    - Parkersburg Community College, 1980-81 (Box 807, Folder 7)
    - West Virginia University, 1980-91 (Box 807, Folder 8)
  - Wisconsin: miscellaneous, 1956, 1990-92 (Box 807, Folder 9)